<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<!-- Created with the Elemental Editor -->
<!-- CoreUnits.xml -->
<!-- -->
<HistoricalFigures>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Draginol">
		<DisplayName>Draginol</DisplayName>		
		<Portrait>Rank_Draginol.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>You, like this mysterious, transcendental figure, have mastered the world and all the things that dwell upon it. Your word is more akin to sacred commandment than secular law; you are more akin to a god than a man. 

Draginol's very existence is little more than rumor; his name appears but a handful of times in the Journals of Ourannes, a Quendar scholar who served Ezmir the scribe on the Long March. His physical appearance is only hinted at therein, never described; he is variously referred to as one of the Destiny, and as separate from them, a being of spirit and energy, radiant with power. 

A single sketch of him, provenance unknown, exists in the library at New Pariden.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>10000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Curgen">
		<DisplayName>Dread Lord Curgen</DisplayName>
		<Portrait>Rank_Curgen.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>Your name is now spoken in hushed whispers; your kingdom is the most powerful on the planet... you, like Curgen before you, are unquestioned ruler of Elemental.

He was most powerful of all the Titans: maker of Imperium, slayer of Pariden, builder of the greatest Empire the world had ever seen. Yet in the end, his own kind turned against him, Arnor and Dred'nir alike, leaving Curgen with none but the Fallen creatures he created as his allies. 

Let his fate serve as warning; do not build your kingdom on the backs and bones of your citizens.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>9000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Pariden">
		<DisplayName>Pariden</DisplayName>		
		<Portrait>Rank_Pariden.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>Glory to your name; glory to the world you have built, the great peace you have ushered in, reminiscent of the golden age of learning and advancement forever associated with the Titan Pariden. 

Though the Age of the Magi is justly remembered as the high point of mankind's civilization, truly the most wondrous era - the most beneficial to all living creatures of Elemental - was that span of time between the arrival of Pariden, first of the Titans, and his murder by Curgen. In that era was the knowledge of mana and its power brought to a zenith; Pariden and his lieutenant Tandis explored not just the continent of Anthuane, but the far seas of the world, and the Veladrii forged the great weapons which are today so justly prized by all. 

If your accomplishments are remembered but half as well, you should deem yourself to be lucky.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>8000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Breon">
		<DisplayName>Breon</DisplayName>		
		<Portrait>Rank_Breon.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>Your achievements make certain that your name will be revered forever in your people's histories, just as the people of the North revere Breon - Witch-Queen of Nimer, guardian of the Magi's Stone; most gifted of all mankind's enchantresses.

She was the savior of the Nimer, the slayer of the Dragon Gokor'as'Saag, from whom she rescued that object which came to be known variously as the Jewel of Breon or the Magi's Stone. Her marriage to Argynn of Malaya united the peoples of this world for the first time in recorded history. Yet for all the things which Breon is remembered, she is most loved for something she lacked: the sin of pride. Though she was Queen of the Nimer, when the librarians of ancient Iluna came to honor her first husband, Aelthir of the Aivern, she gladly stood in his shadow, as she did during the great wars against the Shadow Riders of Parudrah, when Argynn stood as first general of the assembled armies of man.</Backstory>
		<RankScore>7000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Ereog">
		<DisplayName>Ereog</DisplayName>		
		<Portrait>Rank_Ereog.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>The principles by which you built your Empire shall forever stand as an example to other sovereigns, as the teachings of this man -  first and greatest of the Magi - remain a primer for all the world's channelers. 

It was Ereog who cast down Az-Adoras, the Dark Prince, ruler of cursed Al-Ashteroth; and Ereog who raised Hallas from settlement to great city; Ereog who founded the order of Anthuane, whose adherents, known as Padars, journeyed forth across the wide world to teach the worship of the Five. Yet his hour of greatest triumph - the creation of the Forge of Making - was in truth his greatest mistake, for it was the Forge that drew the Titans to Elemental... and ended the rule of man for thousands of years.

Let not your pride in your achievements blind you to their repercussions.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>6000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Lady_Umber">
		<DisplayName>Lady Umber</DisplayName>
		<Portrait>Rank_LadyUmber.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>From chaos you have brought order, overcoming more powerful foes with both might and guile - much as this Titan, once Curgen's most trusted lieutenant, did in forging her own Empire a thousand years ago. 

Men curse her name, for it was the Titan Ilona - known to history as the Lady Umber - who betrayed the flag of truce between Titan and Man and murdered Tandis, captain of the Azure Knights, true commander of the great army of the West. Yet she is beloved of all the Fallen, for Ilona was first to deal with them - Quendar, Urxen, and Trog alike - as worthy beings in their own right, rather than just slaves, as did Curgen.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>5000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Tar-Thela">
		<DisplayName>Tar-Thela, the Emerald Sorceress</DisplayName>
		<Portrait>Rank_Tar-Thela.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>There is much to admire about your kingdom; yet its beauty, like this Enchantress's, disguises the defects within, the flaws that ultimately brought about its downfall.

Of all the Titans who came to this world, few have altered its destiny to the extent this sorceress did, first by her binding of all the world's mana to the elemental shards, then by her seduction and betrayal of Morrigan the Mad. With these acts she was forever cast as a villain, though some claim that in the end, Tar-Thela redeemed herself at the Battle of Imperium by fighting on the side of the Armies of the West.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>4000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Morrigan">
		<DisplayName>Morrigan the Mad</DisplayName>		
		<Portrait>Rank_MorriganTheMad.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>Take greater care in fashioning your empire, lest your fate continue to mirror that of Hosten's son, Morrigan, whose lust for power caused him to descend into madness.

The Patricide, as some called Morrigan, took the throne on his father's death but soon lost interest in the governing of men. What drove Morrigan was a hunger for knowledge - a desire for immortality, to remain young forever, like his paramour, Tar-Thela. In pursuit of that knowledge he reopened the catacombs beneath Imperium, the underground world of Calebethon, and there conducted experiments beyond the ken of Man and Titan... 

His name lives forever in infamy.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>3000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Vatula">
		<DisplayName>Vatula</DisplayName>
		<Portrait>Rank_Vatula.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>You have much to learn, not unlike this sorcerer, a man who should have spent more time mastering his craft and less masterminding his rule.

Vatula came to the channeler's art late in life; a merchant of the House Lamord, he discovered a journal dating from the time before the cataclysm; one that purported to be a comprehensive list of arcane artifacts said to have been amassed by the Scholars of Iluna. He focused his efforts on amassing those objects rather than following the principles of the channeler's art, as outlined in Hosten's Codex. 

His efforts, even when successful, ended in frustration; he lacked the knowledge to utilize the power he possessed.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>2000</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>
	<HistoricalFigure InternalName="Rank_Janusk">
		<DisplayName>Janusk</DisplayName>
		<Portrait>Rank_Janusk.png</Portrait>
		<Backstory>Your current abilities mirror that of Relias's reluctant scribe, a man more suited to hold a tankard of ale than a broadsword. 

Let it not be forgotten, though, that Janusk is a survivor: the only one of Relias's companions to return from the East, one of the only men to emerge unscathed from the burning of Krandir. His tales of Relias's expedition have become required reading in the five kingdoms; the role he played in the Nobles' Revolt is not to be underestimated either. 

Summon a similar resolve in future nation-building efforts, and your efforts will be rewarded.</Backstory>		
		<RankScore>0</RankScore>
	</HistoricalFigure>   
</HistoricalFigures>
